Guide to the Joint Western Area Committee Records, 1965-2004 LAC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- JWAC August 1989 [2/3], 1989 August (Box 124, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1989 [3/3], 1989 August (Box 124, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts CTA
- JWAC November 1989 [1/2], 1989 November (Box 124, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting November 13-17 1989, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1989 [2/2], 1989 November (Box 124, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1990 [1/2], 1990 February (Box 124, Folder 5)
  Agenda Meeting February 12-16 1990, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1990 [2/2], 1990 February (Box 124, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Over the Road Committee, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1990 [1/4], 1990 August (Box 125, Folder 1)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting August 13-17, 1990, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1990 [2/4], 1990 August (Box 125, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings CTA and OTR Committees
- JWAC August 1990 [3/4], 1990 August (Box 125, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1990 [4/4], 1990 August (Box 125, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings CTA Committee
- JWAC November 1990 [1/2], 1990 November (Box 125, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting November 5-9, 1990, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1990 [2/2], 1990 November (Box 125, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1991 [1/2], 1991 February (Box 126, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting February 11-15, 1991, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1991 [2/2], 1991 February (Box 126, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the CTA
- JWAC May 1991 [1/2], 1991 May (Box 126, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting May 6-10, 1991, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1991 [2/2], 1991 May (Box 126, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1991 [1/2], 1991 August (Box 126, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting August 12-16, 1991, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1991 [2/2], 1991 August (Box 126, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1991 [1/2], 1991 November (Box 126, Folder 7)
  November 11-15, 1991, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1991 [2/2], 1991 November (Box 126, Folder 8)
- JWAC February 1992 [1/3], 1992 February (Box 127, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting February 10-14, 1992, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Yellow Freight Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Intermodal Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1992 [2/3], 1992 February (Box 127, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1992 [3/3], 1992 February (Box 127, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1992 [1/2], 1992 May (Box 127, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting May 11-15, 1992, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee
- JWAC May 1992 [2/2], 1992 May (Box 127, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the CTA Committee
- JWAC August 1992 [1/1], 1992 August (Box 127, Folder 6)
  Agenda/Minutes Meeting August 10-14, 1992, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee
- JWAC November 1992 [1/2], 1992 November (Box 128, Folder 1)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting November 9-13, 1992, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC November 1992 [2/2], 1992 November (Box 128, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1993 [1/2], 1993 February (Box 128, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting February 8-12, 1993, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1993 [2/2], 1993 February (Box 128, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1993 [1/2], 1993 May (Box 128, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting May 10-13, 1993, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Local Operations, Yellow Freight Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC May 1993 [2/2], 1993 May (Box 128, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1993 [1/1], 1993 August (Box 128, Folder 7)
  Minutes Meeting August 9-12, 1993, Main Committee, PUD Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Yellow Freight Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC November 1993 [1/2], 1993 November (Box 129, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting November 8-11, 1993, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, Yellow Freight Committee
- JWAC November 1993 [2/2], 1993 November (Box 129, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1994 [1/1], 1994 February (Box 129, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting February 1994, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, PUD Committee
- JWAC May 1994 [1/1], 1994 May (Box 129, Folder 4)
  Minutes, Agenda Meeting May 9-12, 1994, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, PUD Committee
- JWAC August 1994 [1/1], 1994 August (Box 129, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting August 15-18, 1994, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, PUD Committee
- JWAC November 1994 [1/2], 1994 November (Box 129, Folder 6)
  Minutes Meeting November 7-10, 1994, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, PUD Committee
- JWAC November 1994 [2/2], 1994 November (Box 130, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting November 7-10, 1994, Main Committee, Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee, OTR Committee, PUD Committeemittee
- JWAC February 1995 [1/2], 1995 February (Box 130, Folder 2)
  Minutes Meeting February 6-9, 1995, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, PUD Committee, CTA Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1995 [2/2], 1995 February (Box 130, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1995 [1/2], 1995 May (Box 130, Folder 4)
  Minutes Meeting May 8-11, 1995, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries))
- JWAC May 1995 [2/2], 1995 May (Box 130, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting May 8-11, 1995, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1995 [1/2], 1995 August (Box 130, Folder 6)
  Minutes Meeting August 8-11, 1995, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1995 [2/2], 1995 August (Box 130, Folder 7)
- JWAC November 1995 [1/2], 1995 November (Box 131, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting November 6-9, 1995, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1995 [2/2], 1995 November (Box 131, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1996 [1/1], 1996 February (Box 131, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting February 5-8, 1996, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1996 [1/1], 1996 May (Box 131, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting May 6-9, 1996, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1996 [1/1], 1996 August (Box 131, Folder 5)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting August 5-9, 1996, Main Committee, National Grievance Committee, CTA Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1996 [1/1], 1996 August (Box 131, Folder 6)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting November 4-8, 1996, Main Committee, Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee, CTA Committee
- JWAC February 2003 [1/1], 2003 February (Box 132, Folder 1)
  February 2003, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations Committee (summaries and indices)
- JWAC May 2003 [1/1], 2003 May (Box 132, Folder 2)
  Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations (summaries and indices)
- JWAC August 2003 [1/1], 2003 August (Box 132, Folder 3)
  August 2003, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations (summaries and indices)
- JWAC November 2003 [1/1], 2003 November (Box 132, Folder 4)
  November 2003, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations (summaries and indices)
- JWAC February 2004 [1/1], 2004 February (Box 132, Folder 5)
  February 2004, Agenda, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations (summaries and indices)
- JWAC May 2004 [1/1], 2004 May (Box 132, Folder 6)
  May 2004, Agenda, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations (summaries and indices)
- JWAC August 2004 [1/2], 2004 August (Box 132, Folder 7)
  August 2004, Main Committee, Discharge Committee, O-T-R Committee, Change of Operations Committee (summaries and indices)
- JWAC August 2004 [2/2], 2004 August (Box 132, Folder 8)
  August 2004, Proceedings/Transcripts Main Committee, Discharge Committee, PUD Committee, Local Operations, O-T-R Committee
- JWAC Supplements, 1965-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  JWAC Supplements, contract proposals, Western States Area Pickup and Delivery Local Cartage and Dock Workers Supplement
- JWAC Supplements, 1965-2004 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  JWAC Supplements, contract proposals, Western States Area Pickup and Delivery Local Cartage and Dock Workers Supplement: Joint Council #7 Pickup and Delivery Agreement
- JWAC Supplements, 1965-2004 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  JWAC Supplements, Western States Area Office Employees Supplement